<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="status">
        <item>Found</item>
        <item>Lost</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="underline_tv"><u>Sign in as guest </u></string>
    <string name="lostfoundtitle_dialog">Claiming or Helping?</string>
    <string name="lostfoundmsg_dialog">You can add your personal message to the author of this post whether you are claiming the items or helping</string>
    <string name="virtual_den">VIRTUAL DEN. . .</string>
    <string name="email_address">Email address</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="implement_rules">We are strictly implementing one account per one user.</string>
    <string name="close_nav">Close Nav</string>
    <string name="open_nav">Open nav</string>
    <string name="missions_visions">MISSIONS/VISIONS</string>
    <string name="nav_open">nav open</string>
    <string name="nav_close">nav close</string>
    <string name="posted">Posted successfully!</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">156579362556704</string>
    <string name="termsncondition">The terms and condition listed below set forth the terms between the application and the USERS for any service, and features provided by this application.\n

ACCOUNTS:\n
1. Use active email address so that you can activate and retrieve your account password.\n
2. Use only your own student number to get verified.\n
3. Use your real name so other users will know you.\n
4. Hacking and/or manipulating accounts other than your own without permission is prohibited.\n
\n
MESSAGE:\n
1. Flooding or intentionally messaging user repeatedly is not allowed.\n
2. No phornographic conversation in the message will be tolerated.\n
3. Please be polite on messaging other users of the application.\n
\n
LOST AND FOUND:\n
1. Flooding lost and found in any way is prohibited.\n
2. Make sure that your item is posted in the correct category.\n
3. Dont claim item that wasnt yours. Lost and found has records of action done to items.\n
\n
LETTERS FOR DEAN:\n
1. Do not post bad words , system can track and filter it.\n
2.Do not flood the letters for dean area.\n
3. Feel free to suggest and comment but in a good way.\n
\n
DESCIPLINE:\n
1. Respect yourself and other users of this application. Arguing with other users with or without valid reason using insulting words will  never be tolerated.\n
2. Pretension, disguise and or acting as other user and/or person is not allowed.\n
3.Suggestions and complaints will be attended only when an acceptable point has been made. Professors  are not obliged to respond to all PMs unless important.\n
5. Requests are subject to proper screening before vouchsafe.\n
6. Observe good manners and right conduct at all times.\n
\n
VIOLATORS WILL RECEIVE WARNING AT FIRST OFFENSE UNLESS SPECIFIED NOT. WHEN NO ACTIONS WERE DONE TO DEFEND OR CORRECT SUCH ACTIVITY AND/OR CONTINUITION OF VIOLATION, PENALTIES WILL BE APPLIED. TRANSGRESSION PENALTIES MAY cause of disabling an account.
If you have any concerns regarding to your account. Kindly look for the admin of the application ,Sir Jonathan Tomacruz for the assitant.

    </string>
</resources>